(Howard:)So Penny tells me
you're working as a waitress...
(Howard:)...to put yourself through grad school.
That's great.
(Howard:)-What are you studying?
-Microbiology.
(Howard:)Oh, cool. So you could study me.
(Bernadette:)I don't understand.
(Howard:)Microbiology is the study
of tiny living things.
(Bernadette:)I know, I'm studying it.
Yeah, and I said you could study me
because I'm a tiny living thing.
(Howard:)-It's a joke.
-Are you sure?
-Do you like science fiction?
-No.
(Howard:)-Role-playing games?
-Like in the bedroom...
(Bernadette:)...or like Dungeons and Dragons?
(Sheldon:)-Either.
-No.
HOWARD: You like...?
-It's gonna be a long night.
(Penny:)-Yeah, well, it's your fault.
-I had to ask, you didn't have to say yes.
(Howard:)You like magic?